Nicholas Tann

github.com/nicholastann

Professional Summary

Software / Hardware developer and outstanding performer in programming and design within computer engineering. Experienced in full project life cycle from implementation to verification and maintenance.

Skills

- web development: javascript,
 HTML, Jquery, SQL, CSS, Node
- Languages: Verilog, Java,
 C++, Ruby, Python, VBA
- Agile Development

EXPERIENCE

Student Engineering Council, Houston TX - Intern

MAY 2020 - August 2020

• Researched the application of Sentry Technologies' new product "GuardianMT" for structural health monitoring data transmission.

ATSER Engineering INC, Houston TX - Software Development Intern

MAY 2019 - August 2019

 Collaborated in a team to develop the construction management mobile app "FieldIt"

Self Employed, Tomball TX — Private Swim Instructor

May 2016 - Present

• Taught and demonstrated pool safety and competitive swimming strokes, exhibiting proper technique and body position to over 100 swimmers in the Tomball local area.

EDUCATION

Texas A&M University — B.A. Computer Engineering

August 2017 - May 2021

Relative Coursework: Computer Architecture, Software Engineering, Digital Integrated Circuit Design, Microprocessor Systems Design, Linear Control Systems

Involvement

- Campus Crusade for Christ Student Leader
- Member of Freshmen leaders on Campus
- A&M Club Swim National Qualifier
- National Hispanic Scholar